Experience never gets old.
The Intern is a comedy film directed by Nancy Meyers.
70-year-old widower Ben Whittaker has discovered that
retirement isn't all it's cracked up to be.
Seizing an opportunity to get back in the game, he becomes a senior intern
at an online fashion site, founded and run by Jules Ostin.
Ben Whitaker, played by Robert De Niro.
Jules Ostin, played by Anne Hathaway.
Fiona Farwell, played by Rene Russo.
Matt Ostin, played by Anders Holm.
Paige Ostin, played by JoJo Kushner.
Cameron, played by Andrew Rannells.
The Intern is a 2015 American comedy drama film directed,
written, and co-produced by Nancy Meyers.
The film stars Robert De Niro, Anne Hathaway, and Rene Russo.
The plot follows a 70-year-old widower who becomes a senior intern at a fashion website,
where he forms an unlikely friendship with the company's workaholic CEO.
The Intern was released on September 25, 2015, by Warner Bros.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, though De Niro and Hathaway's performances were
praised, and grossed $195 million worldwide against a $35 million production budget.
The film explores themes of new york city, friendship, san
francisco, california, office, masseuse.
The tone is lighthearted and uplifting.